<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CA/NV Amphibian Populations Task Force on California-Nevada Amphibian Populations Task Force</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CA/NV Amphibian Populations Task Force on California-Nevada Amphibian Populations Task Force</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sierra Newt</title>
      <link>/post/test-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/test-post-2/</guid>
      <description>This is a test post. With a Newt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FYLF egg mass</title>
      <link>/post/test-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/test-post-1/</guid>
      <description>This is another test post. With an egg mass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Meetings</title>
      <link>/annual_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/annual_meetings/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Meeting 2021 Meeting: January 14-15, Sonoma County, California. Exact location to be determined.
Previous Meetings   2020 Meeting - San Diego, California 2019 Meeting - Arcata, California 2018 Meeting - Auburn, California 2017 Meeting - Santa Barbara, California 2016 Meeting - Davis, California 2015 Meeting - Malibu, California 2014 Meeting - Beatty, Nevada 2013 Meeting - Arcata, California 2012 Meeting - Placerville, California 2011 Meeting - Yosemite National Park, California 2010 Meeting - No Meeting Held 2009 Meeting - Bodega Bay, California 2008 Meeting - San Diego, California 2007 Meeting - Las Vegas, Nevada 2006 Meeting - Arcata, California 2005 Meeting - Berkeley, California 2004 Meeting - Reno, Nevada 2003 Meeting - Sacramento, CA 2002 Meeting - San Diego, CA 2001 Meeting - Sacramento, CA  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>For more info or to be added to the email list, please contact Dave Bradford (canv.aptf AT gmail.com).
 Interested in getting involved? Please fill out this form!
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>